Guide to the Stanford University, Department of Geology, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Department of Geology, records
1907-1975
SC0164
Stanford University. Department of Geology.
26.5 Linear feet
Student files maintained by the department. The records include grade and attendance records and some correspondence. Also included are departmental minutes, 1922-1973.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Administrative transfer, Department of Geology, 1969, 1977, 1981.
Information about Access
Student records are restricted for 75 years from date of creation.
Description of the Collection
Student files maintained by the department. The records include grade and attendance records and some correspondence. Also included are departmental minutes, 1922-1973.
Access Terms
Stanford University. Department of Geology. Students.; Stanford University. Department of Geology.; College students.
Collection Contents
- Records
  Student records restricted 75 years from date of creation.
  - Student records, 1924-1950
    - Abreu, Ovidio M. (Box 8)
    - Adams, Bradford C. (Box 8)
    - Adams, Elmo Walter (Box 8)
    - Adams, Dr. (soldier) (Box 8)
    - Addington, Arch R. (Box 8)
    - Addison, Carl C. (Box 8)
    - Afshar, F.A. (Box 8)
    - Agnew, A.F. (Box 8)
    - Agosta, D.T. (Box 8)
    - Aguerrevere, Santiago E. (Box 8)
    - Allison, David L. (Box 8)
    - Allison, E.C. (Box 8)
    - Alltucker, John W. (Box 8)
    - Ambrose, Warren Locke (Box 8)
    - Anderson, Frank M. (Box 8)
    - Anderson, Neal Bruce (Box 8)
    - Anderson, R.W. (Box 8)
    - Arleth, K.B. (Box 8)
    - Armstrong, R.A. (Box 8)
    - Arneill, J. (Box 8)
    - Arnold, Newton (Box 8)
    - Arthur, James L. (Box 8)
    - Ashley, John William (Box 8)
    - Atwill, Edward Robert (Box 8)
    - Avery, Paul Walker (Box 8)
    - Ayoinoglu, J. (Box 8)
    - Bailey, Edgar Herbert (Box 8)
    - Bailey, Leo C. (Box 8)
    - Baird, David McCurdy (Box 8)
    - Balch, Marcy F. (Box 8)
    - Barksdale, Julian D. (Box 8)
    - Barlow, George Roger (Box 8)
    - Bastanchury, Ruth F. (Box 8)
    - Bates, Bernarr (Box 8)
    - Bauer, R.M. Jr. (Box 8)
    - Bauman, f.A. (Box 8)
    - Bayles, Robert Ellery (Box 8)
    - Beach, John H. (Box 8)
    - Bean, Robert Taylor (Box 8)
    - Beard, Charles N. (Box 8)
    - Beaudry, C. L. (Box 8)
    - Beenfeldt, Norman (Box 8)
    - Beggs, R.B. (Box 8)
    - Bejach, Wanlyn B. (Box 8)
    - Bell, J.A. (Box 8)
    - Beren, David Oscar (Box 8)
    - Berger, K.H. (Box 8)
    - Berry, C. (Box 8)
    - Berry, R. G., Jr. (Box 8)
    - de Buthune, Pierre (Box 8)
    - Betts, Floyd E. (Box 8)
    - Birch, Donald Courtenay (Box 8)
    - Bixby, R.H. (Box 8)
    - Black, Arthur Whitwell (Box 8)
    - Blosser, Gale Raymond (Box 8)
    - Bourne, W.H. (Box 8)
    - Bowman, E.C. (Box 8)
    - Bradbury, Albert E. (Box 8)
    - Bramel, Hadley (Box 8)
    - Brock, John Malcolm (Box 8)
    - Brock, David (Box 8)
    - Brooks, Baylor (Box 8)
    - Brown, Annabel (Box 8)
    - Brown, Norman (Box 8)
    - Brown, R.A.C. (Box 8)
    - Brown, Randall Emory (Box 8)
    - Browning, Herbert E. (Box 8)
    - Bru (Box 8)
    - Bryner, Leonid (Box 8)
    - Bryant, Jean Marie (Box 8)
    - Buchan, Dean Winslow (Box 8)
    - Bullwinkel, R. (Box 8)
    - Burke, Richard Dryden (Box 8)
    - Bush, John Burchard (Box 8)
    - Butler, Wallace Pierce (Box 8)
    - Cady, James R. (Box 8)
    - Campbell, Charles Duncan (Box 8)
    - Campbell, J.B. (Box 8)
    - Campbell, John Marshall (Box 8)
    - Campbell, William P. (Box 8)
    - Cannon, Robert P. (Box 8)
    - Carlson, D.W. (Box 8)
    - Carpenter, R.B. (Box 8)
    - Cassedy, William P. (Box 8)
    - Cassell, J.K. (Box 8)
    - Cater, Fred W. (Box 8)
    - Chamberlain, J.R. (Box 8)
    - Childs, Theodore Scott Jr. (Box 8)
    - Christensen, Andrew Lee (Box 8)
    - Church, Clifford C. (Box 8)
    - Church, Fermor S. (Box 8)
    - Clark, Carl (Box 8)
    - Clark, Leslie M. (Box 8)
    - Clarke, Robert L. (Box 8)
    - Clute, Walker (Box 8)
    - Cobb, Alfred Burl (Box 8)
    - Cobb, Ed H. (Box 8)
    - Cole, John Gordon (Box 8)
    - Colley, Bernard B. (Box 8)
    - Combs, Guy St.C. (Box 8)
    - Conrad, Robert D. (Box 8)
    - Cook, Earl F. (Box 8)
    - Cook, Lynn (Box 8)
    - Cook, Rufus (Box 8)
    - Coover, Calvin Clay (Box 8)
    - Costantino, Vincent (Box 8)
    - Costello, D.S. (Box 8)
    - Coster, Wilhelmus Johannes (Box 8)
    - Cox, Carroll B. (Box 8)
    - Craggs, D.E. (Box 8)
    - Crimmel, Ray H. (Box 8)
    - Cross, Rodman Kay (Box 8)
    - Crozier, R.N. (Box 8)
    - Crume, Robert W. (Box 8)
    - Curran, John Frances (Box 8)
    - Dake, Helen Elizabeth (Box 8)
    - Davis, Margaret (Box 8)
    - Davison, J.L. (Box 8)
    - Dean, H.S. (Box 8)
    - Debenedette, John Joseph (Box 8)
    - Della-Rose, F.A. (Box 8)
    - Demoss, Edwin C. (Box 8)
    - Denning, Reynolds M. (Box 8)
    - Dennis, Eldon (Box 8)
    - Desisto, John (Box 8)
    - D'Evelyn, Morton Naylor (Box 8)
    - Devlin (Box 8)
    - Dewey, D. (Box 8)
    - Dibblee, Thomas Wilson Jr. (Box 8)
    - Dickson, R. E. (Box 8)
    - Diediker, Paul Lincoln (Box 8)
    - Dodds, Charles (Box 8)
    - Dolloff, N. (Box 8)
    - Donnay, J.D.H. (Box 8)
    - Donnell, J. R. (Box 8)
    - Dorn, Conrad Leopold (Box 8)
    - Drummond, C. Hanford (Box 8)
    - Duran, S.A. (Box 8)
    - Durbin, Robert Alexander (Box 8)
    - Dusenbury, Arthur Newcomb Jr. (Box 8)
    - Dykes, Leland II. (Box 8)
    - Eakland, Edward Hurlburt (Box 8)
    - Earl, Orrin K. (Box 8)
    - Eaton, E.C. (Box 8)
    - Edmundson, James W. (Box 8)
    - Edwards, Page Lawrence (Box 8)
    - Ehrhorn, Charles Springer (Box 8)
    - Elliot, John Fisher (Box 8)
    - Ellis, Gary (Box 8)
    - Ellsworth, Elmer William (Box 8)
    - Erickson, M.P. (Box 8)
    - Evans, David LeC. (Box 8)
    - Falck, Alexander D. (Box 8)
    - Farish, Linn M. (Box 8)
    - Farmin, Rollin (Box 8)
    - Feitler, Stanley (Box 8)
    - Ferguson, R.B. (Box 8)
    - Field, Ross. (Box 8)
    - Finley, W.L. (Box 8)
    - Fisher, Ann (Box 8)
    - Fishman, Ira Leonard (Box 8)
    - Fisher, Max Pinkerton (Box 8)
    - Fitting, Ralph Vit Jr. (Box 8)
    - Fitting, Robert Daney (Box 8)
    - Fletcher, Robert Liester (Box 8)
    - Folsom, Howard William (Box 8)
    - Forester, Joan (Box 8)
    - Forrest, Lesh Clifton (Box 8)
    - Fortier, Yves O. (Box 8)
    - Fowler. Eldridge M. (Box 8)
    - Fox, F.G. (Box 8)
    - Foxhall, Harold (Box 8)
    - Freeman, James (Box 8)
    - Freeman, John C. (Box 8)
    - French, Leigh Hill (Box 8)
    - Fritz, W. D. (Box 8)
    - Frizzell, Don Leslie (Box 8)
    - Frost, Daniel J. (Box 8)
    - Funkhouser, L.W. (Box 8)
    - Gabbert, Howard M. (Box 8)
    - Galbraith, A. Montgomery (Box 8)
    - Galliher, Ed gar Wayne (Box 8)
    - Gamel, Stanley Warren (Box 8)
    - Gandy, Archie Harry (Box 8)
    - Gariepy, Glen B. (Box 8)
    - Gates, Geo. O. (Box 8)
    - Gebhaidt, Elton Guy (Box 8)
    - Gill, Joe Powers (Box 8)
    - Girard, C.M. (Box 8)
    - Glasser, M.M. (Box 9)
    - Goose, Kurt (Box 9)
    - Gordon, MacKenzie Jr. (Box 9)
    - Gray, David Thomas (Box 9)
    - Green, Charles Frederic (Box 9)
    - Green, George Leroy (Box 9)
    - Green, J.W. Jr (Box 9)
    - Gregersen, Albert I. (Box 9)
    - Gribi, E.A. (Box 9)
    - Gribbin, David James (Box 9)
    - Griffin, George Alonzo (Box 9)
    - Griggs, A. B. (Box 9)
    - Griswold, Bruce Pardee (Box 9)
    - Gros, Frederick C. (Box 9)
    - Grothaus, Louis C. (Box 9)
    - Hackel, Otto (Box 9)
    - Hall, J. Allan Jr. (Box 9)
    - Hancock, Bob (Box 9)
    - Hansen, William (Box 9)
    - Harrington, William C. (Box 9)
    - Harris, John S. (Box 9)
    - Hart (Box 9)
    - Hastings, Douglas D. (Box 9)
    - Hedberg, Ballis D. (Box 9)
    - Heidel, Carl C. (Box 9)
    - Heikkila, H.H. (Box 9)
    - Heins, Paul S. (Box 9)
    - Helm, Mary (Box 9)
    - Henry, James Melvin (Box 9)
    - Herold, Stanley C. (Box 9)
    - Hicks, C.L. (Box 9)
    - Hicks, John S. (Box 9)
    - Higazy, Riad (Box 9)
    - Hill, D.M. (Box 9)
    - Hobson, Henry David (Box 9)
    - Hochman, L. (Box 9)
    - Holliday, Samuel (Box 9)
    - Hollis, Eleanor M. (Box 9)
    - Holloway, Murray S. (Box 9)
    - Holmes, Leffel E. (Box 9)
    - Holmes, C. N. (Box 9)
    - Hoskins, E.G. (Box 9)
    - Howe, Mortimer C. (Box 9)
    - Howell, F. W. (Box 9)
    - Hoyt, R.G. (Box 9)
    - Hubbard, Roy K. (Box 9)
    - Hughes, Donald D. (Box 9)
    - Hughes, Ross H. (Box 9)
    - Humphrey, Frederic G. (Box 9)
    - Hunt, Charles Warren III (Box 9)
    - Hutchins (Box 9)
    - Hyde, Benjamin Cooper (Box 9)
    - Isotoff, Andrei I. (Box 9)
    - Ito, Tomo (Box 9)
    - Ivanhoe, L.F. (Box 9)
    - Iverson, Richard J. (Box 9)
    - Jackson, Harry W. (Box 9)
    - James, Allan (Box 9)
    - James, Le. (Box 9)
    - James, Larry (Box 9)
    - Jehanbani, N. (Box 9)
    - Jenkins, Olaf P. (Box 9)
    - Jewitt, W. (Box 9)
    - Jimenez, Luis A. (Box 9)
    - Johnson, Floyd L. (Box 9)
    - Johnson, Frederic Albion (Box 9)
    - Johnson, H.S. (Box 9)
    - Johnson, Rolfe S. (Box 9)
    - Johnson, Yard M. (Box 9)
    - Johnston, Francis Newlands (Box 9)
    - Johnston, P.M. (Box 9)
    - Johnston, William P. (Box 9)
    - Jones, Hal (Box 9)
    - Jones, Ira (Box 9)
    - Jordan, Lee Knight (Box 9)
    - Kalenborn, Fred M. (Box 9)
    - Karren, R.J. (Box 9)
    - Kartehner, Wayne Elisha (Box 9)
    - Keenan, Marvin Francis (Box 9)
    - Key, Carlos (Box 9)
    - Kildale, Malcolm Bruce (Box 9)
    - Killingsworth, C.C. (Box 9)
    - Kinkel (Box 9)
    - Kirchen, Harold Walter (Box 9)
    - Kirk, Howard M. (Box 9)
    - Kirkpatrick, Roger Knox (Box 9)
    - Kirwan, Gerald Maitland (Box 9)
    - Klein, Ira E. (Box 9)
    - Kleinpell, Robett Minssen (Box 9)
    - Knouse, Stanley (Box 9)
    - Kornfeld, Moses Marion (Box 9)
    - Kurfess, Jim (Box 9)
    - Lachenbruch, M.C. (Box 9)
    - Landenberger, John Carroll Jr. (Box 9)
    - Lavender, Dwight Garrigue (Box 9)
    - Lechich, George Paul (Box 9)
    - Leibold, Louise (Box 9)
    - Leigh, R.E. (Box 9)
    - Lemmon, Dwight Moulton (Box 9)
    - Leroy, L.W. (Box 9)
    - Lewis, A. (Box 9)
    - Lewis, James Ogier (Box 9)
    - Linville, R. G. (Box 9)
    - Lippman, F.A. (Box 9)
    - Liscomb, R. L. (Box 9)
    - Livermore, John S. (Box 9)
    - Lockhart, A.A. (Box 9)
    - Lombard, L.V. (Box 9)
    - Loofbourow, Robert L. (Box 9)
    - Lund, Oswe Trelfa (Box 9)
    - Lungeford, H.D. (Box 9)
    - Lynch, John Caldwell (Box 9)
    - Lynn, Bernard Stanley (Box 9)
    - Lynn, Harold F. (Box 9)
    - Lyon, R.R. (Box 9)
    - MacDonald, G.H. (Box 9)
    - McAllister, James Franklin (Box 9)
    - McBride, G.B. (Box 9)
    - McClintock, Frank (Box 9)
    - McConnell, Duncan (Box 9)
    - McCormick, Evan D. (Box 9)
    - McCreary, Bruce D. (Box 9)
    - McCroder, T. (Box 9)
    - McDivitt, Wallace W. (Box 9)
    - McDonald, James Alexander (Box 9)
    - McFadden, John Andrew (Box 9)
    - McFadden, R.C. (Box 9)
    - McKee, George Washington (Box 9)
    - McKinlay, P.F. (Box 9)
    - McLain, J.P. (Box 9)
    - McMasters, John Herbert (Box 9)
    - McNab, James (Box 9)
    - McNeil, Walter Carson (Box 9)
    - McPherson, W.J. (Box 9)
    - Mahoney, Rolland F. (Box 9)
    - Maio, C.G. (Box 9)
    - Maitland, William B. (Box 9)
    - Mannon, William H. (Box 9)
    - Mapel, W.J. (Box 9)
    - Marier, E. L. (Box 9)
    - Marks, J. G. (Box 9)
    - Marsell, R.E. (Box 9)
    - Martin, Lois T. (Box 9)
    - Mastin, C.D. (Box 9)
    - Mathews, Richard Donald (Box 9)
    - Mattingly, lV.E. (Box 9)
    - Manzy, Rosalie Jane (Box 9)
    - Maya, Evans Blakemore (Box 9)
    - Meadows, Edwin Perry (Box 9)
    - Mecia, Anthony J. (Box 9)
    - Meikle, John B. (Box 9)
    - Melcon, Zenas Kurken (Box 9)
    - Menish, Jack (Box 9)
    - Miller, Gardner Burnham (Box 9)
    - Millikin, Paul Hynes (Box 9)
    - Miranda, Leandro Jose (Box 9)
    - Misz, J.B. (Box 9)
    - Mitchell, Hermane Jr. (Box 9)
    - Mohr, J. Henry (Box 9)
    - Moran, William Rodes (Box 9)
    - Morris, Lawrence Kendall (Box 9)
    - Morris, lvlurr (Box 9)
    - Morrisey, N.S. (Box 9)
    - Morrison, Harry Clifford (Box 9)
    - Morrison, Larry Lester (Box 9)
    - Morrison, R.B. (Box 9)
    - Morton, Robert Henry (Box 10)
    - Moses, Selma (Box 10)
    - Mulryan, J.D. (Box 10)
    - Munns, Edward Jay (Box 10)
    - Murphy, Thomas D. (Box 10)
    - Murray, Jack Edwin (Box 10)
    - Murray, R.C. (Box 10)
    - Myers, D.A. (Box 10)
    - Myers, Earl H. (Box 10)
    - Myers, Robert (Box 10)
    - Myers, Wm. Howard (Box 10)
    - Nauss, Arthur William (Box 10)
    - Neel, Henry Howard (Box 10)
    - Nesheim, G. D. (Box 10)
    - Nesbit, Robert Allen (Box 10)
    - Neuman, James Vincent (Box 10)
    - Newby, Chester A. (Box 10)
    - Newton. William A. (Box 10)
    - Nichols, Gaylord E. (Box 10)
    - Nichols, James Ross (Box 10)
    - Nicol, David (Box 10)
    - Norman, Lewis Arthur Jr. (Box 10)
    - Nuffield, Edward Wilfred (Box 10)
    - Nurmi, Rudolph (Box 10)
    - Ogden, Ann (Box 10)
    - Olsen, Clinton Louis (Box 10)
    - Olsen, John Walter (Box 10)
    - Olsen, R.P. (Box 10)
    - Onder, Kasim Ekrem (Box 10)
    - Oneill, Donald B. (Box 10)
    - Oneill, J.L. (Box 10)
    - Oltman, Charles E. (Box 10)
    - Osborne, Lee S. (Box 10)
    - Otamendi-Blanco, Paul (Box 10)
    - Page, Benjamin Markam (Box 10)
    - Paguirigan, Francisco (Box 10)
    - Pantin, J.H. (Box 10)
    - Parks, Ernest K. (Box 10)
    - Parsons, K.R. (Box 10)
    - Partridge (Box 10)
    - Patchett, Margaret Lynn (Box 10)
    - Patten, John M. (Box 10)
    - Peake, A. Lee (Box 10)
    - Pearson, Virginia M. (Box 10)
    - Peck, Edward Hurlbut (Box 10)
    - Peirce, Fred L. (Box 10)
    - Penn, William Y. (Box 10)
    - Penny, Dolores (Box 10)
    - Perrin, Frances Ward (Box 10)
    - Phillips, B.C. (Box 10)
    - Phillips, Norman (Box 10)
    - Plate, Horatio (Box 10)
    - Playter, John Carpenter (Box 10)
    - Poland, Joseph (Box 10)
    - Post, Henry B. (Box 10)
    - Pratt, William Held (Box 10)
    - Ptasynski, H. (Box 10)
    - Puck, Raymond (Box 10)
    - Putnam, William Clement (Box 10)
    - Putlitz, Fritz H. (Box 10)
    - Quackenbush, William M. (Box 10)
    - Quinsey, Bob (Box 10)
    - Ransome, Alfred Leslie (Box 10)
    - Raymond, Ralph H. (Box 10)
    - Reed, Ralph D. (Box 10)
    - Reel, Cecil E. (Box 10)
    - Reese, U.R. (Box 10)
    - Rehm (Box 10)
    - Reiley, D.C. (Box 10)
    - Reinhart, Philip Wingate (Box 10)
    - Renquist, Melvin Leroy (Box 10)
    - Reynolds, Carl (Box 10)
    - Richards, George Lambert (Box 10)
    - Richards, Lawrence Wayne (Box 10)
    - Riddell, Charles Edwin (Box 10)
    - Ritts, L.C. (Box 10)
    - Roark, Louis Claude (Box 10)
    - Roberts, Chauncey (Box 10)
    - Roberts, E.E. (Box 10)
    - Roberts, Fred B. (Box 10)
    - Robins, A. R. (Box 10)
    - Rogers, Jack B. (Box 10)
    - Rose, Robert Harlod (Box 10)
    - Rose, Stanford Leland (Box 10)
    - Ross, John A. (Box 10)
    - Rumbley, Jane Elizabeth (Box 10)
    - Rust, Cameron Ralph (Box 10)
    - Ryan, T. Antoinette (Box 10)
    - Ryan, B.W. (Box 10)
    - Salvador, A. (Box 10)
    - Sawyer, Joe Herbert (Box 10)
    - Sayler, Charles H. (Box 10)
    - Scales, John C. (Box 10)
    - Schaetti, Henry (Box 10)
    - Schaub, H.P. (Box 10)
    - Schenk, Edward T. (Box 10)
    - Schirm, John Stephen (Box 10)
    - Schoonover, F.E. (Box 10)
    - Scott, Walter E. (Box 10)
    - Scull, B.J. (Box 10)
    - Severy, Charles Luther (Box 10)
    - Shaw, Stanley (Box 10)
    - Sheldon, Dean Howell (Box 10)
    - Shipkey, Arthur Herbert (Box 10)
    - Shupe, R. (Box 10)
    - Silberling, N.J. (Box 10)
    - Simon, Louis J. (Box 10)
    - Simons, Frank S. (Box 10)
    - Simpson, Charles Jerry (Box 10)
    - Singer (Box 10)
    - Sinnott, Allen (Box 10)
    - Skala, Hubert Jan (Box 10)
    - Sloss, Laurence L. (Box 10)
    - Smith, Fred E. (Box 10)
    - Smith, Colin H. (Box 10)
    - Smith, George James (Box 10)
    - Smith, Glen Murray (Box 10)
    - Smith, Hamilton Allen (Box 10)
    - Smith, Julian (Box 10)
    - Smith, Kernick (Box 10)
    - Smith, Merritt Burdette (Box 10)
    - Smith, R.A. (Box 10)
    - Smith, W.A. (Box 10)
    - Smith, Ward Conwell (Box 10)
    - Snedden, Loring Bertram (Box 10)
    - Sohlberg, Rudolph Gust (Box 10)
    - Spencer, Jean Stephen (Box 10)
    - Staples, Lloyd W. (Box 10)
    - Stearns, William Roland (Box 10)
    - Steiny, Thomas R. (Box 10)
    - Stelck, C.R. (Box 10)
    - Stepens, John Carnes (Box 10)
    - Stevenson, W.H. (Box 10)
    - Stipp, Thomas Franklin (Box 10)
    - Stopper, Robert Fr ancis (Box 10)
    - Storey, Herbert Cushing (Box 10)
    - Strain, W.A. (Box 10)
    - Strom, R.H. (Box 10)
    - Sturz, C. (Box 10)
    - Sugar, E. (Box 10)
    - Sumpf, Robert (Box 10)
    - Swayze, Helene (Box 10)
    - Switzer, George (Box 10)
    - Swope, Richard G. (Box 10)
    - Taber, R. (Box 10)
    - Taber, Edward Carroll (Box 10)
    - Taylor, Perry Norman (Box 10)
    - Taylor, William Harlan (Box 10)
    - Teale, Jack Nelson (Box 10)
    - Teneyck, Richard G. (Box 10)
    - Theobald, P. (Box 10)
    - Thomas, Leo A. (Box 10)
    - Thomas, R.G. (Box 10)
    - Thompson, J.C. (Box 10)
    - Thompson, Thomas F. (Box 10)
    - Thompson, Warren O. (Box 10)
    - Thorup, Richard Russell (Box 10)
    - Tillia, John Henry (Box 10)
    - Todd, Wallace (Box 10)
    - Tolman, Frank B. (Box 10)
    - Tolman, John Van Steen (Box 10)
    - Tomlinson, Warren E. (Box 10)
    - Tranger, F.A. (Box 10)
    - Treacy, Harold (Box 10)
    - Tremel, Paul (Box 10)
    - Tretzger, R.E. (Box 10)
    - Troster, J.G. (Box 10)
    - Trueblood, Marg C. (Box 10)
    - Ulloa, Salvador (Box 11)
    - Valentine, William W. (Box 11)
    - Vandenbus, Alfred I. (Box 11)
    - Van Voorhis, Bartow (Box 11)
    - Vergastegui, P.M. (Box 11)
    - Verhoogen, Jean (Box 11)
    - Vidos, A. (Box 11)
    - Vincent, Jack C. (Box 11)
    - Vonderkuhlen, Henry C. (Box 11)
    - Von Estorff, Fritz F. (Box 11)
    - Walker, G.W. (Box 11)
    - Wallace, K. G. (Box 11)
    - Walton, Albert S. (Box 11)
    - Washburn, Edward D. (Box 11)
    - Wasson, F. B. (Box 11)
    - Waterhouse, John C. (Box 11)
    - Waterman, Glenn (Box 11)
    - Watson, Elizabeth A. (Box 11)
    - Watson, J.E. (Box 11)
    - Webster, C. (Box 11)
    - Weller, Arthur Reilly (Box 11)
    - Wells, J.D. (Box 11)
    - Westheimer, J erome (Box 11)
    - Warton, Jay Bigelow (Box 11)
    - Wheatfil1, Edward Lewis (Box 11)
    - Wheeler, Harry Eugene (Box 11)
    - White, Donald E. (Box 11)
    - White, Gordon Ashbridge (Box 11)
    - White, Robert T. (Box 11)
    - Whiteman, A. (Box 11)
    - Whitley, W.W. (Box 11)
    - Widmer, Kembel (Box 11)
    - Wigmore, J.G. (Box 11)
    - Wilcken, Phyllis D. (Box 11)
    - Williams, Harriet Louise (Box 11)
    - Williams, Marjorie (Box 11)
    - Willis, R. B. (Box 11)
    - Willis, T .H. (Box 11)
    - Willson, D. (Box 11)
    - Willson, Leslie E. (Box 11)
    - Willson, Lloyd Kenneth (Box 11)
    - Wilson, Stephen Ray (Box 11)
    - Wiss el, John F. (Box 11)
    - Woodward, Albert F. (Box 11)
    - Worts, George F. Jr. (Box 11)
    - Wright, Richard E. (Box 11)
    - Wyant, Donald G. (Box 11)
    - Wyman, T.S. (Box 11)
    - Young, J.E. (Box 11)
    - Zielbauer, Edward J. (Box 11)
    - Zimmerman, John (Box 11)
    - Zwang, Herman Cecil (Box 11)
  - Student records, 1948-1967
    - Abell, Webster Philips (Box 5)
    - Adams, John B. (Box 5)
    - Adent, W.A. (Box 5)
    - Agnew, John Dewolf (Box 5)
    - Agverreverre, J. (Box 5)
    - Aguiar, G.A. (Box 5)
    - King, Janet Louise (Box 5)
    - (Mrs. Alexander) (Box 5)
    - Albrizzio, Carlos E. (Box 5)
    - Albers, John P. (Box 5)
    - Allen, John D. (Box 5)
    - Aliaga, Elias A. (Box 5)
    - Allen, Gary Curtiss (Box 5)
    - Almanza, Eliseo (Box 5)
    - Ancieta, Hugo Alfonzo (Box 5)
    - Anderson, A.T. (Box 5)
    - Anderson, J. Fergus (Box 5)
    - Anderson, R.A. (Box 5)
    - Anderson, Roger Yates (Box 5)
    - Apfel, John Jos. (Box 5)
    - Armstrong, F. C. (Box 5)
    - Arnold, H.O. (Box 5)
    - Atakan, Hizamettm (Box 5)
    - Atchley, Frank W. (Box 5)
    - Atwill, Edw. Robt. (Box 5)
    - Austin, Clem C. (Box 5)
    - Avary, Edw. R. (Box 5)
    - Ayres, M. (Box 5)
    - Aytug, Necla (Box 5)
    - Ayala, Agustin (Box 5)
    - Bai 11y, P. (Box 5)
    - Baker, A.T. (Box 5)
    - Baker, Ronald D. (Box 5)
    - Barbat, Wm. M. (Box 5)
    - Barber, Richard Wastell (Box 5)
    - Barbosa, DeCarvalho K.W. (Box 5)
    - Barnard, Michael Paul (Box 5)
    - Barnes, Wm. C. (Box 5)
    - Barnola, Alberto (Box 5)
    - Barrow, Brian M. (Box 5)
    - Barr, Edw. S. (Box 5)
    - Barrow, T.D. (Box 5)
    - Baum, Lawrence Frederick (Box 5)
    - Beall, Arthur Oren, Jr. (Box 5)
    - Bea 11, John (Box 5)
    - Beck, Myrl Emil (Box 5)
    - Becker, Victor Howard (Box 5)
    - Beeman, Jeffrey H. (Box 5)
    - Beie, Rolf (Box 5)
    - Belosic, E.G. (Box 5)
    - Benson, G. T. (Box 5)
    - Bernheim, Philippe (Box 5)
    - Berry, Donald W. (Box 5)
    - Berry, Fred (Box 5)
    - Bereridge, Alexander (Box 5)
    - Bhanjdeo Swaroop (Box 5)
    - Bhatt, Kireet (Box 5)
    - Bickell, Robt. S. (Box 5)
    - Birkeland, Peter (Box 5)
    - Binger, Jas. MacKnight (Box 5)
    - Bjerke, Chester (Box 5)
    - Blacet, Philip Merrell (Box 5)
    - Blake, Milton Clark (Box 5)
    - Blanchard, Maxwell Blaire (Box 5)
    - Blaustein, M.K. (Box 5)
    - Blenk, Marianne Elizabeth (Box 5)
    - Bonilla, Geo. Manual (Box 5)
    - Bonner, Albert S. (Box 5)
    - Born, Robt. Maynard (Box 5)
    - Bowers, S.D. (Box 5)
    - Bowyer, Ben (Box 5)
    - Boyd, Francis (Box 5)
    - Brabb, Earl E. (Box 5)
    - Bradley, Wm. C. (Box 5)
    - Brant, David M. (Box 5)
    - Brew, David Alan (Box 5)
    - Brooke, Robt. C. (Box 5)
    - Bromell, John Del (Box 5)
    - Bronson, Chas. Ronald (Box 5)
    - Brooks, Stephan A. (Box 5)
    - Brown, Eugene (Box 5)
    - Brown, Theron (Box 5)
    - Brown, Walter Wm. (Box 5)
    - Brown, Willis R. (Box 5)
    - Bryant, Donald L. (Box 5)
    - Bryant, Donald G. (Box 5)
    - Bryant, Robt. C. (Box 5)
    - Buder, Theodore A. (Box 5)
    - Bugge, John E. (Box 5)
    - Butt, Wm. (Box 5)
    - Burch, Stephen Howell (Box 5)
    - Burchfied, Burrell C. (Box 5)
    - Burdan, Robt. (Box 5)
    - Burford, Robt. (Box 5)
    - Burke, H.H. (Box 5)
    - Burke, John Randall (Box 5)
    - Burkhardt, Scott (Box 5)
    - Burkland, Philip Vincent (Box 5)
    - Burrows, John Wilfrid (Box 5)
    - Burtner, Roger Lee (Box 5)
    - Bushnell, David Clifford (Box 5)
    - Buss, Halter R. (Box 5)
    - Camacho-Costro, Mario (Box 6)
    - Caddy, Terry Miles (Box 6)
    - Cameron, l'im. Lang (Box 6)
    - Campbell, C.V. (Box 6)
    - Campbell, F .L. (Box 6)
    - Carlson, Stewart J. (Box 6)
    - Castle, R.O. (Box 6)
    - Castro, Lu is (Box 6)
    - Carson, Matthew V. (Box 6)
    - Carver, John A. (Box 6)
    - Castillo, Rolando (Box 6)
    - Chittick, Edw. H. (Box 6)
    - Christian, Louis B. (Box 6)
    - Christiansen, Robt. L. (Box 6)
    - Chuber, Stewart (Box 6)
    - Cheeley, Emmet D. (Box 6)
    - Classen, Jas. Stark (Box 6)
    - Clum, Guy C. (Box 6)
    - Coe, Wm. C. (Box 6)
    - Colburn, Ivan P. (Box 6)
    - Clark, Dana K. (Box 6)
    - Cole, Alexander T. (Box 6)
    - Coleman, R. (Box 6)
    - Constable, R.W. (Box 6)
    - Cook, John S. (Box 6)
    - Corliss, John Burt (Box 6)
    - Corvalan, Jose (Box 6)
    - Cox, Clint Rudolf (Box 6)
    - Cox, Dennis (Box 6)
    - Cox, Raymond Lee (Box 6)
    - Crandall, Bradford G. (Box 6)
    - Cresswell, Geo. (Box 6)
    - Crosby, Don C. (Box 6)
    - Crosier, Dwight Tipps (Box 6)